Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火B字幕合闫SubindexV0.5
Created time 13.07.11 10:31:10
孩子们 在我大学二年级时
Kids, sophomore year of college,
Lily阿姨刚放完春假回来
when Lily came back from spring break,
Marshall叔叔在机场给了她个惊喜
Marshall surprised her at the airport.
而她也用一箱六支装本地产啤酒 给了他惊喜
And she surprised him with a six-pack of locally brewed beer.
_德岱堡! 明白?
Fort Lau-ger-Dale! Get it?
随之产生了一项传统
And with that, a ritual was born.
接下来的11年里 他俩无论何时
For the next 11 years, whenever either of them would fly anywhere...
飞往何处... - Minne-Cider
Minne-Cider!
了解?
Get it?
重逢的庆祝总是伴随着
... the reunion was always commemorated with a chauffeur sign
一个司机手势和一箱带回来的 六支装当地啤酒
and a six-pack from wherever they'd been.
Aspen Yards Ale!
收到?
- Get it? - Actually, no.
其实 没有
Me, neither. I was hoping you would.
我也是 我还以为你会懂
但是在2009年一月的一晚
But, one night in January of 2009, the unthinkable happened.
难以想象的事情发生了
- I'm not picking her up. - What?
- 我不去接她 - 什么?
Lily不想我搭出租一路赶去机场
Lily doesn't want me taking a cab all the way to the airport
只是为了再搭一辆回来 明白吧?
just to take a cab all the way back, you know?
但六支装当地啤酒呢?
But the six-pack thing.
Ted... 年轻时那算是情趣
That stuff was fun when we were younger, but we've grown past that.
但我们都过了那个年纪了
我们的感情也随着我们成熟起来了
As we mature, the relationship matures with us.
但是... 我是说 你们俩对我们这些人
But... you guys are such an inspiration to the rest of us,
是很大的激励  你们这么恩爱跟亲密
how you're so devoted and connected.
我看着你们
I look at you guys, and that's all I want in the whole world.
觉得那就是世界上我想要的全部了
Ted 外面有两个女大学生 看上去挺好泡的!
Ted, there's two college girls outside, and they look easy!
那么 亚利桑那州
Arizona, you know,
我- 我一直想瞧瞧
I've always wanted to see what an Arizona driver's license looks like.
亚利桑那州驾驶执照长啥样
这招我刚才已经用过了 兄弟 她们21岁啦
I already ran that play. They're 21.
- 明白啦 - 老天爷 嗯 那你们来镇上是干嘛?
We're good. Thank God. So, what brings you guys to town?
我们乐队有个演出机会
- Our band's got a gig. - Oh, you're in a band?
噢 你们参加了乐队?
- 嘿 或许我们可以去看你们表演 - 失陪一下
- Maybe we'll come see you play. - Excuse us for a sec.
Ted 你到底怎么回事?
What is the matter with you?
- 我们不会去看她们的演出 - 为什么不去?
- We're not gonna go see them play. - Why not?
要是我们去看她们演出
If we see them play, we're no better
那我们就像是那些Van Halen音乐会上
than the bleach-blonde bimbos who flash their boobs at a Van Halen concert.
蠢到冒泡的胸大无脑的金发妞
是啊 但那些小妞在演出后不是
But don't those girls get to have sex with Van Halen after the show?
跟Van Halen上床了吗?
你要是想和Van Halen上床
If you want to have sex with Van Halen, do it on your own time.
那就别在工作时间里 Ted
我们不是那种
We are not the maybe-we-can-come- see-you-play guys.
"或许我们能去看表演"的家伙
我们是另外的 更成熟的男人
We're the other guys, the older guys who never showed up
从不现身 总是被人们所热切追求
and whose approval they now crave.
那我们算是她们的老爸了?
- So we're their dads? - Exactly.
正是
好吧
有个重要的会议
It's a big meeting, so I don't think we're gonna make it.
所以我们去不了了
或许下次吧 姐们
Maybe next time, kiddos.
但要是你们想在演出之后见面
If you want to meet us after your show, maybe we could exchange numbers.
- 或许我们能交换电话号码... - 失陪一下
Excuse us for a minute.
Ted 你脑子进水了啊?
Ted, have you gone completely insane? We don't want their phone numbers.
我们不想要她们的电话号码
是 我不知道我在做什么
I don't know what I was doing. I guess I panicked out there.
我想我在外面那儿有点慌张
当你跟一个小妞交换号码时
When you exchange numbers with a chick,
她们可以拨打或是直接删掉
you give them the ability to call and cancel.
你要是定个约会 不用号码
If you set a date without a number, they have to show up.
她们就必须出现了
见面 嘿咻!
Check and mate!
我唯一需要的"数字"(也指"手指") 就是这些
The only digits I need are these.
哦呵
Honka.
你还是他们的老爸吗?
Are you still their dad?
我们不如明晚10点在这见吧
So, why don't we just meet here tomorrow night around 10:00.
我想得看雪下得怎样
I think it's supposed to snow.
要是有暴风雪我们怎么办?
- What do we do if there's a blizzard? - Either way, we'll be here.
不管怎样 我们都会到的
下雪问题
"Snow" problem.
最后再失陪一会
Excuse us just one last second.
现在又是怎么回事?!
What is the problem now?
干得好
- Nice one. - Thanks.
好的 明晚见
- We'll see you tomorrow night. - Totally. Awesome!
- 一定到 - 好极了!
"一定到 好极了!"
"Totally. Awesome!"
老兄 那些大学小妞感觉挺蠢
Man, these college chicks sound stupid.
一定到 好极了
- Totally. - Awesome. So, here's the thing:
现在的情况: 明晚
tomorrow night, dress to move; it's gonna be a mess!
穿衣打扮 到时候一定轰轰烈烈
我还是觉得我们应该拿到她们的号码
I still think we should've gotten their numbers.
你老是杞人忧天
You always assume something is gonna go wrong.
Ted 我向你保证 绝不会出什么岔子
Ted, I promise you, nothing is gonna go wrong.
嘿 开始下雪了
It's starting to snow.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com== 老爸老妈浪漫史 第四季第13集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：老妖 猴猴 校对：小白 时间轴：里知
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Arrow
孩子 09年的暴风雪狂暴无比
Kids, the blizzard of '09 was a monster.
雪一直下了三天
It snowed for three days straight,
也带来了三个难忘的故事
which led to three amazing stories.
我从Barney跟我的故事讲起
I'll start with me and Barney.
外面环境糟透了
It's pretty nasty out there. I don't think they're coming.
我想她们不会来了
Of course they're coming. They have to.
她们当然会来了 那是必须的
要是我能把到其中一个妹
If I can land just one of these girls, I'll have party school bingo.
我可就中了玩乐学校的大奖啦
拜托 Ted 这儿只有你一个人
Come on, Ted. You're the only one here.
哦 不好意思 什么是玩乐学校大奖?
Sorry. What's party school bingo?
每一年"花花公子"都会列出一个
Every year, Playboy releases a list of the top party schools in the country.
全国最顶尖的玩乐学校的名单
我选了前25名 然后做了个...
I take the top 25, and I make up...
大奖卡片
a bingo card.
我需要亚利桑那科技大学
All I need is Arizona Tech,
狂热的地方
which is crazy.
在联盟赛里 通常会有
In league play, that would normally be designated a free space.
指定的自由空间
那么 在你那个玩乐学校大奖里
So, how many people are in on this party school bingo thing?
有多少个人?
哦 就我一个
It's just me.
那这些事都有什么意义?
So what's the point, then?
意义在于我连续搞定5个
The point is to get five in a row.
在那之后呢?
And what do you get when you get five in a row?
我就中大奖啦
I get bingo.
多谢你能过来
Thanks for coming by.
我在这恒温器上花了一个小时
I monkeyed around with the thermostat for about an hour
然后才发现它是内部通话系统
before I realized it was the intercom.
我在楼下听到你的骂声了
I heard you swearing downstairs.
嘿 那么
So, Lily's flight's coming in tonight, you're really not gonna go pick her up?
Lily的班机今晚就到了
你真不打算去接她吗?
Robin Robin 就像我说过的
我们的感情随着我们成熟起来了
Like I said,
as we mature, our relationship matures with us.
是啊 我了解你妻子
Yeah, if I know your wife,
她还是会给你带六支装啤酒的
she's gonna get you that six-pack anyway.
Marshall?
Puget Stout
Puget Stout.
西雅图最可口的啤酒
A most exquisite Seattle microbrew.
说到六...
And speaking of six-packs...
噢...
你要干嘛?
- What are you doing? - I'm going to the airport.
我要去机场
我怎么会这么蠢?!
How could I be so stupid? Of course she's bringing me a six-pack!
她当然会给我带六支装啤酒了!
但这次 我没有给他带六支装啤酒
But this time, I didn't bring him a six-pack.
因为...
Because... as we mature,
我们的感情随着我们成熟起来了
the relationship matures with us.
听上去他是个不错的年轻人
He sounds like a nice young man.
我猜他一定还是会给你个惊喜 会来接你的机
I'll bet he surprises you and picks you up anyway.
- 噢 宝贝! - 喔 喔
喔 喔 喔
我的啤酒呢?
- Where's my beer? - We said we weren't gonna.
我们说好不再搞这些的
- 我这儿有啤酒 - 哇哦
I have beer.
是六支装的 而且你的身高跟我正合适
A six-pack and you're an appropriate height for me.
出发 新Lily
Let's go, New Lily.
哦 我得弄点啤酒来
- Man, I got to get some beer. - Folks, this is your captain speaking.
乘客们 我是本机的机长
我们即将提前一小时
Looks like we're going to be arriving an hour early.
到达
太好啦! 呜呼!
赶紧喝完 伙计 我要关门了
Drink up, boys. I'm closing the bar.
不要啊! 才刚9点而已
- It's only 9:00. - And this place is ragin', yo!
这里气氛正热烈着呢
伙计 非常抱歉 但我得去弄
Guys, I'm really sorry, but I got to go set up cots in the church basement.
教堂地下室的帆布床了
It doubles as a shelter on snowy nights like this.
在这样的雪夜里它就是个避难所了
你这个自私的混蛋!
You selfish bastard!
有两位辣妹正来这儿见我们
There are two very hot girls coming here to meet us.
你就不能迟点再关门吗?
Can't you leave open a little while longer?
我们会看着一切的
- We'll keep an eye on everything. - You two? No way.
你们俩? 算了吧
You wouldn't know the first thing about running a bar.
你们连经营一家酒吧最重要的事 都不知道
先为辣妹服务?
Serve the hotties first?
钥匙在这里
Here's the keys.
那些女孩一到
As soon as your girls show up, you turn off the lights and you lock up.
你们就得关灯锁门
我不想回来看到这里一片狼藉
I don't want to come back and find this place trashed.
哇 你说真的?
- Seriously? - I can trust you guys.
我信任你们俩
To understand what it meant to us to get the keys to MacLaren's,
为了让你们了解能得到Maclaren的钥匙
对我们意味着什么 让我们回到几年前
I have to take you back a few years
那个我说了五个单词的晚上
to the night that I uttered five little words
那是每个男人在他生命某个时刻 都会说的
that every man at some point in his life will say.
咱该开酒吧
- We should buy a bar. - Of course, we should buy a bar!
当然 我们应该买一家酒吧!
我们就是应该买一家酒吧
We should totally buy a bar.
- We should totally buy a bar. - Our bar would be awesome.
我们的酒吧一定棒极了
老兄 老兄
And dude, dude, dude,
老兄 老兄...
dude...
我们酒吧的名字...
the name of our bar...
谜题
Puzzles.
人们不禁会想
People will be like, "Why is it called Puzzles?"
"为什么叫做谜题?"
那就是个谜
That's the puzzle.
那是...
That is...
一个绝妙的酒吧名字!
a great name for a bar!
而且
And also, at Puzzles:
在谜题: 不会催赶客人
no last call.
不会赶客人!
No last call!
只有当每个人都喝完了
Only when every single person is finished having the greatest night
度过了一个人生中最美妙的夜晚
of his or her life do we stack the chairs on the table
我们才开始收拾桌椅
关掉三层的玛格丽塔酒瀑布
and power down the three-story margarita waterfall.
我们应该买一家酒吧
- We should buy a bar. - We should buy a bar.
就像每个男人都会说的
Like the other ill-advised five-word sentences
另外的五字蠢话...
every man eventually says in his life...
我能跳过去
I can jump that far.
把她抢回来
I'm gonna win her back.
我信任你们俩
I can trust you guys.
我们早晚会后悔的
... we would come to regret it. We just didn't know it yet.
只是当时不知道
你有货?
You have it? Awesome! I'll be right there.
太棒了 我马上就到
Ranjit!
你好
I'm Rachel Sondheimer.
我是Rachel Sondheimer
等一分钟 Lily
Wait a minute, Lily.
如果你刚下飞机 那Marshall在哪儿?
If you are getting off the plane, where is Marshall?
还有你的六瓶装呢?
- And where is your six-pack? - That's the problem.
那就是问题所在
I have to get to Brewniverse in East Meadow in an hour.
我得在一小时内
赶到东梅多的Brewniverse
跟我上车吧!
- To the Town Car! - Thank you.
哦 谢谢!
哦 酒保
Barkeep. Triple Sec.
橙味利口酒 (triple sec:"三重蒸馏" 代表橙味利口酒)
Coming right up, tap-minder.
立刻就来 伙计
哈 哈 噢 嘿!
我们再买一个
We'll get one.
上酒
- Order up. - Order up.
我们再买一个
We'll get one.
谢天谢地 你们还在这儿
Thank God you're still here.
不知道你们有没有
I don't know if you guys have ever seen Star Wars, but it's like Hoth out there.
看过星球大战 但外面就象霍斯星球 (Hoth:星战中被冰层覆盖的行星)
- 这个我要 - 让我想起
Dibs.
我常和老爹滑雪橇...
It reminds me of when I used to go sledding with my dad...
在他去世之前
before he left.
这个是我的
And dibs.
那 来杯酒暖暖身 怎么样?
So, can we warm you up with a drink?
当然... 顺便说一下 我邀请了
Sure... by the way, I invited the rest of the band to come and meet us.
乐队其他人来这和我们碰头
我们希望能喝醉
We were hoping to get drunk. I mean really drunk.
我是说酩酊大醉
像我老爹过去那样
Like my dad used to.
别跟我抢 别跟我抢
Dibsity, dibsity, dibsity.
我想我们能
I guess we could keep the place open a little bit longer.
迟一点再关门
只要就你们和乐队
As long as it's just you and the band.
Melissa
Melissa, what kind of band is this?
你们是什么乐队?
哦 我们是亚利桑那打击科技母鸡行进乐队
We're the Arizona Tech Fighting Hens Marching Band.
母鸡向前冲!
Go, Hens!
于是 我和你们的Barney叔叔
And then, your Uncle Barney and I had one of our telepathic conversations.
展开了一次心电感应对话
伙计 Carl会剁了我们
Dude, Carl's gonna kill us
如果我们不赶紧把所有人都踢出去的话
if we don't kick everyone out of here right now.
Barney 我是认真的
Barney, I'm serious. We promised we wouldn't mess the place up.
我们保证过不会 把这里弄得乱七八糟
好吧 你说的也对
All right, I guess you have a point.
酒吧继续营业!
The bar is open!
谁要啤酒?
Who wants a beer?
我还是会说这很蠢
I still say this is stupid.
"我们的感情随着我们成熟起来了"
What happened to, "As we mature, the relationship matures with us"?
怎么回事?
那是Lily在"今日心理"上看到的
That's just something Lily read in Psychology Today.
好啦 是在"时尚"上看到的
All right, she read it in Cosmo.
好啦 是我在"时尚"上看到的
All right, I read it in Cosmo.
好啦好啦 是"娇点" (针对年轻女孩子的版本)
All right, it was Cosmo Girl. Just drive, okay.
你就管开车 行吧
我只是不懂一个小惯例
I don't get why it's such a big deal
被搁在一旁有什么大不了的
that one little ritual goes by the wayside.
不只是这样 懂吗?
It's not just this, okay? It's all our little rituals.
是我们所有的小习惯
你知道以前每天我一回家 我们都要做什么吗?
Do you know what we used to do every day the second I got home?
老兄 我可不想听你们 那疯狂的猴子激情
Man, I don't want to hear about your crazy monkey sex.
我们会告诉对方当天吃过的东西
We would tell each other what we had to eat that day.
两个鸡蛋 一片奶酪批萨
Two eggs, a slice of cheese pizza
还有一些水煮蔬菜
and some steamed veggies.
综合贝果 鸡胸肉
Everything bagel, chicken breast,
一些西芹棒 和一勺花生酱
some celery sticks and a spoon of peanut butter.
疯狂的猴子激情?
- Crazy monkey sex? - Crazy monkey sex.
疯狂的猴子激情
噢 Lily TMI
信息过多
TMI...
too many informations.
你知道我还怀念什么吗?
You know what else I miss?
我们的午餐电话
Our lunchtime phone call.
嘿 宝贝 午餐时间了 我爱你
Baby, it's lunchtime, and I love you.
原则上我应该与你交换
I reciprocate in principle.
尽管伴随诉讼的中止
Although with the caveat that there seems
貌似在我这有稍许剩余
to be a bit of a surplus here on my end.
不 我更爱你
No, I love you more.
我们需要找个房间
Do we need to get in a room together and bang this thing out?
迅速解决这事吗?
所开出的条件听上去很合我意
Those sound like agreeable terms,
尽管我可能得
although I may need adjust my briefs.
调整我的案情提要
我也爱你
Love you, too.
但今天当她打过来
But today when she called,
我由着它转接到语音信箱 语音信箱!
I let it go to voice mail. Voice mail!
你怎么能?!
How could you?!
我最怀念的是
The thing I miss most is kissing at midnight on New Year's Eve.
除夕子夜的那一吻
那可是新年传统
It was a New Year's tradition.
但你知道今年我们干了什么吗?
But you know what we did this year?
- 疯狂的猴子激情? - 才不是
- Crazy monkey sex? - No.
- 好了 所有这些看似可爱的小习惯 - 确实...
Okay, all these cute, adorable little rituals... They're stupid.
它们都很无聊
Telling each other what you had to eat? You're like children playing house.
告诉彼此吃过些什么?
你们就像两个孩子扮家家酒
唔... 可能你觉得它们无聊
Maybe you just think they're stupid because you've never been
那是因为你从没和某人交往
in a relationship long enough to develop them.
久到养成这些习惯
什么?!
- What? - You don't understand love.
你不懂什么是爱
好吧 你就像机器人
Okay, you're like some robot who sees a person crying and says...
看到有人哭就说...
"为什么这个人类在漏水?"
"Why is that human leaking?"
- 就是那样吗? - 没错
Is that right?
那...
Well, then... Robot initiating pull-over-to-the- side-of-the-road-
启动机器人程序
把车开到路边
until-jackass-apologizes- to-me sequence.
直到混蛋向我道歉
我的机器人程序要好上几千几万倍
My robot was like, a million times better.
嘿 就跟你说一声
So you know, the trough in the bathroom is overflowing.
厕所的水槽满得溢出来了
厕所没水槽
There's no trough in the bathroom.
你刚从厨房出来
And you just came out of the kitchen.
Ted 奎宁杜松子酒怎么调!
What's in a gin and tonic? What's in a gin and tonic?
奎宁杜松子酒该怎么调?!
好啦 开酒吧太逊了
Running a bar sucks. Let's just close up.
我们关门吧
不! 不!
There's no last call.
不要搞什么最后招待
迷情酒吧 这是Barney
Puzzles, go for Barney.
还好 你还在那 我五分钟就到
Good. You're still there. I'll be there in five.
最后招待
Last call.
Robin 来了辆除雪机
There's a snowplow coming. We have to get back on the road.
我们得回到路上
You think the only way to be in love is to have pet names.
你以为爱情唯一的方式就是喊出些爱称
或给对方留些愚蠢的小字条
Or leave each other stupid, little notes
或毫无缘由地驾车
or go charging off into a blizzard for no good reason.
冲进暴风雪中
Do you understand what's going to happen?
说真的 你明白
除雪机经过会发生什么吗?
You know what you are? You're a love snob.
你知道你是什么吗? 你是个爱情势利鬼
两人交往有很多方式
There's lots of ways to be in a relationship,
你不会懂的
you would know that if you ever left your little love snob country club.
除非你摆脱爱情势利乡村俱乐部
我们要被雪埋了
We're going to get buried by snow. That's going to happen.
逃不掉了
No, screw this. I'm not going to sit here and be insulted.
不 去你的吧
我不会干坐在这里被你羞辱
我们不去机场 我们回家
We're not going to the airport. We're going home.
这是怎么了
What just happened?
嘿 嘿 嗨!
We called earlier about the Seattle microbrew.
先前我们电话问过西雅图本土品牌啤酒
哦 对 还好你打了电话
Good thing you called when you did. I was getting ready to close up.
那会 我准备要关门了
外头可是下着世纪之雪
Storm of the century out there.
当然 现在只是09年 所以说是世纪之雪
Of course, it's only '09, so storm of the century might be
可能有点过了
a little bit premature.
还是说年度之雪吧
Let's say storm of the year.
但现在只是一月份
Although, it is only January.
我们很急 我们现在就得拿走啤酒
We're in kind of a hurry, so, we'll take the beer now.
你们真是可爱的一对
You are a cute couple.
- 谢谢 - 我们不是一对
- Thank you. - We're not a couple.
谢天谢地 要不然太诡异了
Thank God. That would be weird.
那...
她来了
Here she is.
"超音速奎宁"
"Supersonic Tonic."
不 这是个桶
No. This is a keg. I need a six-pack.
我要六连装
- A keg's all I got. - We'll take the keg.
我只有这个桶
那我们就拿这个
What? Oh, no. Last time I had one of these in the car,
什么? 噢 不
上次我车里载这个
我最后不得不用油灰刀把座位上
I wound up chipping dried vomit off the seat
干掉的呕吐物刮掉
with a putty knife.
抱歉 Ranjit 但这是我们的惯例
I'm sorry, Ranjit, but this is a ritual
我要把这桶啤酒带给他
and I am bringing him this beer.
你能不能帮我搬进车里
If you could just put it in the car.
我给你50块
I'll give you 50 bucks.
跟我上车吧!
To the Town Car.
Robin 我很抱歉
Robin, I'm sorry. You're not a robot.
你不是机器人
就算你是 你也是
If you are, you're, like, an incredibly advanced model,
非常先进的型号
人类根本没机会
and the human race doesn't stand a chance.
你只是不在俗套的惯例中
You just don't choose to show your love
展现你的爱 那没关系
through corny rituals, and that's fine.
但可能我和Lily这么做
But maybe the reason Lily and I do is because we always have,
是因为我们一直这么做
and we don't know any other way.
我们也不知道其他方式
我清楚地知道一件事 那就是
One thing I do know is that
如果她独自坐在机场
if she's there sitting at the airport alone,
我必须得去接她
I have to go get her.
这些是我们的原则
Those are the rules.
Marshall 闭上眼睛
Marshall, close your eyes.
我不懂你怎么会
I don't know how you heard any of that as me hitting on you, but...
以为我在和你调情 但...
照做吧
Just do it.
现在我们去接你的女人
Now let's go get your woman.
好嘞 走吧
All right, come on.
你们不一定要回家 但不能呆在这儿
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
我总巴望着这么说话
I've always wanted to say that.
我是说 在酒吧里
I mean, in a bar. I say it all the time at home.
我在家一直这么说
伙计 哪天我们应该买个酒吧
Dude, someday we should buy a bar.
等我们买了
And when we do, we are never going to have last call.
我们决不赶客人走
想想 Barney
Come on, Barney. We said no last call. We've got to mean it.
我们说过不会有最后招待
我们得说话算话
Well, what are we supposed to do? Carl's going to be here any minute.
那 我们该怎么做?
Carl随时会回来的
我们能做的只有一件事
Only one thing we can do.
伙计 开酒吧实在麻烦
Dude, running a bar is a pain in the ass.
我们应该在自己的圈子里闯荡
We should just stick with what we know.
我们该组个乐队
- We should start a band. - Of course we should start a band!
我们当然该组个乐队!
我们之前怎么都没组乐队?
How have we not started a band yet?
孩子们 有时生活
Kids, sometimes in life the planets align,
就像连成线的行星 凡事排成排
everything links up,
而你会遇到最完美的时机
and your timing is perfect.
Marshall?
Lily?!
Lily?
这一刻并非如此
This wasn't one of those times.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
西雅图
Seattle.
- 什么? - 她的航班被取消了
- What? - Her flight's canceled.
根本没起飞
It never took off.
不 不 那样她会打给我...
She would've called me and...
嘿 宝贝 是我
Baby, it's me.
我的航班因为什么暴风雪被取消
My flight's been canceled because of some snowstorm
我得到周四才能再订到票
and they couldn't rebook me till Thursday,
所以我得在这再呆两天
so I'm stuck here for another two days.
但这是午餐时间 我爱你
But it's lunchtime, and I love you.
就像我说的 暴风雪持续了三天
Like I said, this was a three-day storm.
周二
- Tuesday. - I still say this is stupid.
我还是会说这很蠢
周三
Wednesday.
周四
- And Thursday. - ... microbrew.
先前打电话问过西雅图本土品牌啤酒
所以当Marshall周二听到那则留言...
So on Tuesday when Marshall heard that message...
她得到周四才回来
She's not coming in till Thursday.
我是说 我们
I mean, we came all the way down here, and she's not coming in till Thursday.
花大力气来这里
而她得到周四才回来
我觉得我好蠢
I feel so stupid.
你瞧 我们...
Look, let's just, let's not tell Lily about any of this, okay?
别把这事告诉Lily 好吗?
尤其是你和我调情那段
Especially the part about you hitting on me.
我没和你调情
I didn't hit on you.
一点没错
Exactly.
然后在周三... 噢 老兄
Then on Wednesday...
我不敢相信你刚开车兜了个大圈
Man, I can't believe you drove all the way out there.
现在你又准备
Now you're gonna turn around and drive all the way out there again tomorrow.
明天再花力气开过去
不是的 这整件事是个征兆 你知道吗?
是时候让惯例休息了
This whole thing was a sign, you know? It's time to put that old ritual to bed.
我不打算去接她
I'm not going to pick her up.
Robin真的勾引你了?
Robin really hit on you?
伙计 感觉怪怪的
Dude,
it was weird.
兄弟们 这个派对赞啊!
Bros,
this party is awesome!
你是我们打击母鸡的真朋友
You are true friends of the Fighting Hens.
如果需要什么
If you ever need anything, don't hesitate to ask.
尽管张口 别客气
吹长笛的有男朋友吗
Is the flute section seeing anyone?
那 等等 你真的不去接她?
So, wait, you're really not going to pick her up?
是 真的啊
- Really. - So the New Year's kiss,
那除夕之吻
午餐电话
the lunchtime phone calls, the whole
还有"说说今天吃过什么"
"this is what I ate today" thing, you're really letting it all go?
你 这一切你真的就这么算了?
真的算了
I really am.
接着 我们来到了周四
Which brings us to Thursday.
一个松饼 一个熏牛肉三明治 一包薯片
A muffin, a pastrami sandwich,
我知道早过了午餐时间 但我爱你
and a bag of chips.
And I know it's way past lunchtime, but I love you.
每天都越爱越多
More and more each day, I love you, Lily.
我爱你 Lily
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
等一下 这是不是意味着
Wait, does this mean that I have to bring a marching band to the airport
从今以后我得
- 带支行进乐队来机场? - 当然啦
- from now on? - Absolutely.
完蛋了
Crap.
Go, Hens!
谜题
Puzzles.
这个乐队名真棒
That is a great band name.
嘿 你看到Amanda了吗?
Have you seen Amanda?
正点!
Bingo!
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入